<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andre Afonso</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Andre Afonso</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 04:50:20 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Owasp Juiceshop</title>
      <link>/posts/owasp-juiceshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 04:50:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/owasp-juiceshop/</guid>
      <description>Some things that were unsolved that I found out in the demo version :)
Target: OWASP Juice Shop
 Bully Chatbot&amp;nbsp;¶ You have to release your inner nagger and ask repeatedly for coupons :)
What worked for me was to type coupons +=1
 Repetitive Registration&amp;nbsp;¶ This one is pretty simple.
Fill out everything correctly, then go to the first &amp;ldquo;Password&amp;rdquo; field and change it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static website with wordpress? No thanks!</title>
      <link>/posts/static-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 01:47:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/static-website/</guid>
      <description>I had a fancy shmancy website with wordpress, and I was very proud! Nice pentest tooling logos, badges for showing off, great header image. But besides terrible loading times, 3 hours to set up a 2min reading time blog post or hard time customizing css&amp;hellip; none of that really showed what I was actually learning or even who I really became after entering the cybersec world.
 Then, in a video of my brother David, I remembered that his guest Graham Helton (great guy) had a great website!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey there,</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 20:02:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I like coffee&amp;hellip; a lot!
Just like most night owls in the cybersecurity space :)
If you ever talk to me, you&amp;rsquo;ll understand I&amp;rsquo;m a curious guy that likes to ask questions about almost everything. I love to learn, that&amp;rsquo;s why Google is a good friend of mine!
Professional XP&amp;nbsp;¶  2021 - Cybersecurity Professional @ Siemens 2017 - Digital Marketing Manager @ TIPS4Y 2010 - Several Marketing and Consulting roles  Trainings&amp;nbsp;¶  Scrum &amp;amp; Kanban CompTIA Security+ Cisco Introduction to Cybersecurity   Don&amp;rsquo;t let anything get in your way, specially if it is to reach me out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>picoCTF web exploitation writeups</title>
      <link>/posts/picoctf-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 23:42:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/picoctf-web/</guid>
      <description>Hey, this is a simple writeup on the challenges provided by picoCTF
Hope you find it useful ;)
 Get aHEAD&amp;nbsp;¶ For this challenge you should think about the HTTP request methods (GET, POST, PUT, DELETE, HEAD,&amp;hellip;)
See the HEAD there? Does it look like something you have on the title of the challenge? xP
The HEAD gives you the website&amp;rsquo;s metadata. It should do the same thing as a GET but without all the body, although sometimes they are different.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
